hey everyone thanks for listening to
grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Krakowski and in this podcast I
talk about how to build a coaching
business a course business your mindset
as well as marketing strategies
leadership strategies
and ways to be more successful
now today I'm going to talk about how to
use the energy of other people
to create your persona in your business
and
this is kind of an interesting
topic because
obviously we want to be authentic we
want to be ourselves we don't want to be
a copy of other people
but when it comes to like the coaching
and online course space
I think there's
something to being a student of other
teachers and listening to other teachers
coaches mentors
who share what's on their heart
and the ones that you like you like
their Style
you like how they talk how they
communicate the Nuance of their language
things like that you sort of
mirror them in the beginning
not like what their content is
but rather their energy their tone
how they pause the way that they
structure sentences the way that they
rise in their energy and they come down
low and
and
observing
how these other speakers and other
leaders
do that now
you could you could learn
all the Nuance of this in a book go to
college
whatever
I didn't do that I just listened to a
bunch of podcasts
and
opted in for a bunch of
offers and webinars and trainings that
other people did
and just watched other teachers teach
and then as I
observed them teaching
I would then teach my own content from
the energy of how they taught
one way that you can do this is like
watch a podcast episode
for 30 minutes before you have to record
your own training you can watch my my
podcast
if you like my energy if you like how
I connect and how I communicate with
people
you can then borrow that
and use it for your own
recordings your own trainings your own
courses podcasts social media content
is plug into the stuff that I'm making
watch maybe a whole podcast episode from
me
um
listen to uh
a training that I did
listen to a training that I did
specifically I think I stepped on a
a nail or something I don't know
those if you're watching me on video I
just like paused that was weird it
wasn't a nail though
watch the different trainings that I do
and
then go and record your own thing
go and record your own content
what ends up happening is it's like
especially if you're actively listening
you're not like passively listening it's
kind of like where you're actually
paying attention you ever gotten amped
up
lit up excited
by somebody talking about a certain
topic
what I like to do is I'll watch
specifically
the the piece of content that that
person has that makes me feel that way
and then I will immediately go out
and make my content a lot of our clients
and our client growth accelerator
say that after the weekly training that
we do that they go and they record their
ads or they record their trainings and
things like that oftentimes I will
record
trainings and podcast episodes and
pieces of content
after my live coaching call with my
coaching clients as well because I'm in
that mindset I'm in that mind state
of where I was
with the people that have actually hired
me to work with me
and this is a piece of
content that I was talking to our group
about today
was that
if you don't feel confident in your own
skin
making content
like I don't know if I sound good enough
I don't know if I look good enough
things like that first off let me say
this how you look
um has no impact in
how far you go out there
um
make yourself feel your best that's the
most important thing when you show up
show up in a way where you feel your
best
but don't filter it through expecting
judgment from other people that they're
not going to accept you you're not going
to like you not going to want to listen
to you so that's one of the first things
is we have to start by accepting
ourselves
we have to start by accepting that we
are
Worthy
worth people listening to
worth people giving their time to listen
to us
and that
other people will love to listen to us
now I hope that people will listen to me
not I hope I'm good enough
but actually believing and declaring
that you're amazing
and then anybody who doesn't want to
listen to you well they're just missing
out
and actually holding on to that belief
listen I get that your life may be
telling you something else
that's your life experience maybe
telling you that you're not good enough
that you haven't reached an enough level
to be able to do this
it's it's completely up here
it's completely in how we think about
ourselves and it has nothing to do with
reality of how much we performed
how much we've done
what we've accomplished
it's 100 up here now by accomplishing
things
it does elevate
your level of confidence and you become
more unshakable
but that level of confidence comes in
before the result comes in
and so what you need to do is you need
to cultivate in yourself showing up
at the highest state when you go out and
create your Facebook ads when you go out
there and do your
live sales presentations
when you do your courses when you do
your training
when you make your podcast when you make
content also
the more often
you actually record content of yourself
the more often you
show up
to connect and communicate and talk to
an audience
whether it be pre-recorded or live
the more often you do this the more
comfortable you're going to get at it
and the better you're gonna get at it as
well if you're somebody who doesn't feel
confident at doing this type of stuff
the more you do it while you don't feel
confident the more that you show up even
though you don't think you're good
enough
you will get better
at it
whatever that thing is that you're
trying to get better at and what I would
recommend that you do is not just a
bunch of social content
not just a bunch of
podcasts or YouTube videos but
content that people actually have to
register for
give you their name and email address
for
Live Events a free training some kind of
a training where people are going to
sign up to listen to you and if you do
it a few times where you're actually
showing up live
where you're actually connecting with
people
live
not just pre-recorded not just a
recording where you press the camera and
record it but you're actually
taking the risk of getting people in
front of you on a live presentation to
where you can't turn it off
I'm sure you could kick everybody out of
the room but once they're there you're
gonna have to show up
you're going to have to connect you're
going to have to communicate and that
might be the scariest thing in the world
but you need to put yourself into
situations
where you
do what terrifies you
where you take that Terror terrifying
action
to grow in that confidence
and so then
for you to grow in that confidence
it starts by you
mirroring
somebody else
it starts by you
finding your own favorite teacher
favorite speaker favorite podcaster that
you can mirror
and
sort of imagine yourself of like what
would they do if they were me in this
situation
how would they connect
how would they communicate
how would they
show up
and so then by doing that
you're able to show up in your highest
level of power
you're not trying to show up as them
like you're not trying to be them
and do what they do
but rather answering
if I was them and they were trying to do
what I'm trying to do how would they do
it I'm going to say that again
you're not trying to be this other
person and do what they're doing and say
word for word what they say that's
called plagiarism
you're
you're saying okay if this person
was doing what I'm doing
how would they show up
how would they communicate
how would they connect some guys that I
always think about Ed my lap Bradley
uh Andy frizzella
these different podcasters that I listen
to initially
when I started my podcast that really
I
have been inspired by them I've been
inspired by their message I've been
inspired by how they talk by how they
communicate and so then when I show up
I always say how would they show up
in this situation if I'm feeling a lack
of confidence if I'm not feeling like
I'm connected to how I really want to
show up and present myself to the world
okay so this will help you
when you're making content
just when it comes to the nuance
you're essentially acting
you're essentially playing the role
of the future version of yourself
before that actually becomes the reality
and again I'm not talking about
fabricating
information I am a multi-millionaire
when you're not and lying to people and
defrauding people that's not what I'm
talking about at all
what I'm talking about
is you
showing up
boldly courageously
where you're at right now
having gratitude for where you're at
you're not trying to be somewhere else
you're not trying to
Force things to happen you're actually
thankful for where you're at in the
process because of what you're learning
right now that's one of the first things
you need to do not become
disappointed dissatisfied upset that
you're not where you want to be and that
comparing yourself to other people
that's just gonna hurt you
and that's going to keep you held back
longer
by operating from that type of energy
where you're you're
wishing you were somewhere else that you
aren't right now
we have to let go
and detach
from needing to force future events to
happen
we need to detach from how we thought
things should go and demanding and
requiring and now I'm devastated because
it didn't go my way I see people do this
all the time
they write me
they
spent 200 on Facebook ads and they
didn't become a millionaire overnight
and now they are completely disheveled
and their life is over in their mind
and I don't hear from them again for two
years
because they they didn't have the
ability to handle
what was going on they didn't have the
what life they were creating they
weren't ready to handle that at that
level and they were so attached to how
they thought something should go that
they connected their happiness joy
safety security
to this outcome working out perfectly
how they imagined
people like that
are always disappointed
they're always playing the victim
they're always angry
at everybody else
about what they're not doing right
they're always critical of themselves
and other people
they're always
beating themselves up
they're always punishing themselves for
making mistakes
and they live a really sad existence
that
truthfully comes from honestly
having a hard life
possibly experiencing abuse
for most of these people
trauma
childhood trauma
adult trauma corporate trauma relational
trauma
this type of
abuse
locks your brain into
looking for sure things
and being risk-averse
to where you're afraid
of taking a risk to where you're afraid
to do something that you can't a hundred
percent control that you can't a hundred
percent guarantee how it's going to go
foreign
and I understand that there's a lot of
people who listen to my podcast that
that's you that's why you've been stuck
you're afraid of
a runaway credit card when you run
Facebook ads so you won't run Facebook
ads because you're so afraid of
something that you can't control taking
over you and harming you
because that's what you have experienced
in your life as you've experienced so
many things being forced on you against
your will and being controlled by other
people and situations that you fight
back
against anything that feels like that
and then when you launch your business
it feels like your abuser
your business feels like
the person who hurt you the most
or you project that onto your mentor
or your coach
because you're looking for somebody to
be responsible when the truth is it's
just right up here
it's right up here
and when we learn
to operate in our highest state
our highest energy for me I look for how
can I manage my state to be the happiest
and most joyful at all times going for
walks around my neighborhood helps me do
that
eating
drinking water throughout the day not
sacrificing my self when it comes to
oh I'm working so hard on the project or
I'm taking care of my baby so much that
I have no time to drink water and take
care of my own health
that's actually a
response from trauma to do that to where
your me your needs weren't able to be
met
and that you had to constantly manage
and control
other people for Safety and Security
that you sacrifice your own needs my new
baby just came this last week and I
literally found myself doing this
not eating not drinking water
not doing what I know will take care of
me to operate in my highest
state of joy and happiness
and so that's one of the first things
is do more of what makes you happy more
often instead of waiting until you've
reached a certain goal to experience joy
and happiness
instead of waiting until things go your
way to feel happy you cultivate it from
inside of you right now in any situation
no matter how you need to do that
whether it be through prayer or faith or
you just go out and have some fun or you
play a video game or whatever that thing
is for you that helps you operate from
that highest state you just do that more
often right before
you go record your content
you go create your sales letter
you go do the things that you're trying
to do what I'll do it'll do is it'll
snap you I told some people to do this
before they go to run their Facebook ads
often
because they're operating from this fear
programming this
avoid pain programming this avoid
getting hurt by the algorithm
programming and so you have to snap
themselves into a positive State of Mind
to actually break the physiology that
they're feeling inside of them that's
telling them avoid avoid avoid attacker
attacker you're under attack that puts
you into hyper vigilance to try to avoid
getting hurt and all you're just doing
is running Facebook ads all you're doing
is just using chat GPT all you're doing
is just creating a Jasper account
but your body and your brain think that
it's something far more dangerous and so
you actually have to snap yourself out
of that by doing more of the things that
you love more of the things that make
you happy
more often
and exercise
controlling your energy controlling your
state instead of being controlled by how
you feel you actually say okay I'm not
feeling my best right now I want to
shift into
the state of mind that I can operate out
of my best that I want to shift out of
feeling this lack of confidence and I
want to
for and maybe just for 30 minutes
or 45 minutes let's say you have a sales
presentation that you need to do you
want to shift into this confident State
of Mind for about 45 minutes to do that
sales presentation where you might
normally have been timid you might
normally have been afraid but you find
okay I can find a window
or a pocket of time
to shift into this state of mind so like
I'll go for a walk I'll play a video
game I'll go listen to a podcast that'll
get me excited and then I'll go out
there and I'll record my Facebook ads or
I'll go out there and I'll write my
sales copy
when you do this
you can actually start to decide and
dictate
what happens in your life
you're not subject to
just letting your feelings Define what
you can do and how much you can do each
day
you're actually a lot stronger than you
realize when you learn how to control
your state of mind
State Management
and these are some of my methodologies
I've never learned this like
clinically or studied this much this is
just what I do myself to manage my own
State and it's helped me tremendously
and I think it'll help you as well
grow your life everybody
we'll talk soon listen this has helped
you at all share it with somebody don't
keep this to yourself
let the world know about the grow Your
Life podcast have a good one